Welcome to the jungle!
Meet the Feebles is a comedy, music, fantasy film directed by Peter Jackson.
Heidi, star of the "Meet The Feebles Variety Hour" discovers
her lover Bletch the Walrus is cheating on her.
And with all the world waiting for the show, the assorted co-stars must contend with
drug addiction, extortion, robbery, disease, drug dealing, and murder.
Samantha the Cat / The Sheep (voice), played by Donna Akersten.
Sebastian / Dr. Quack / Daisy the Cow / Sandy the
Chicken (voice), played by Stuart Devenie.
Heidi / Robert / Barry the Bulldog (voice), played by Mark Hadlow.
Wynyard the Frog / Trevor the Rat / The Fly (voice), played by Brian Sergent.
Harry / Dennis / Abi Bargwan / Mr. Big / Pekingese / others
(voice) (uncredited), played by Ross Jolly.
Bletch / Arfur the Worm (voice), played by Peter Vere-Jones.
Meet the Feebles (also known as Frogs of War in New Zealand as the film's English fake working title) is a 1989 New Zealand adult puppet musical black comedy film directed
by Peter Jackson, and written by Jackson, Fran Walsh, Stephen Sinclair, and Danny Mulheron (who also performed the body of lead character Heidi the Hippo).
The plot follows a stage troupe of anthropomorphic
animals in a perverse comic satire.
In contrast to the positive innocence and naïve folly of The Muppets, the Feebles
largely present negativity, vice, and other misanthropic characteristics.
The film is the first Jackson co-wrote with his future partner Fran Walsh,
with the two collaborating on all his subsequent films.
The film also marked the beginning of Jackson's collaborations with Richard Taylor and Wētā Workshop,
as created by Taylor and Tania Rodger, who all worked on Jackson's subsequent films.
The film explores themes of pornography, sexual abuse,
drug addiction, musical, celebrity.
The tone is lighthearted.